Right, Fuyutsuki-sensei?
You! You really are
despicable!
I knew from the start he was
a dangerous person!
It's because of people like this
that us proper people suffer.
No matter how much private lives
are supposed to be private,
this is going too far.
The girls in our class are saying
they're so scared
that they won't be able
to come to school!
Um, well, everyone, this...
But you know, I think my body
might be a little better.
Not that I'm bragging.
So you want Fuyutsuki-sensei
to see it?
Kotani-sensei, please!
Hey, this is the Nakano Queen.
What is that?
It's a famous S&M club.
Why do you know about that,
Teshigawara-sensei?
Uh, well...
In any case, this undoubtedly
is another problem.
Would you believe me?
I never remember this!
Then why is this here,
how do you explain this!
Well, you see...
That's right! I've got
a huge scar from
a fight when I was
in high school.
If you see that...
What are you doing!
Aren't you embarrassed at all
being caught like this?
And you've just started at
this school!
Do you have any proof
otherwise?
I'm getting the director!
Director! It's me!
Open up! It's about Onizuka!
What are you going to do?
Director!
Teacher, so that's what
you're into?
Could it be that you're looking
at us in that way too?
How scary!
How do we explain this
to our parents?
We can't tell them that
our homeroom
teacher is into S&M,
can we?
Who was it?
I know it was one of you.
Just be honest and tell me,
and I'll forgive you.
- Teacher.
- What is it, Kikuchi?
- Do you have any proof?
- No, that's not...
Then please don't accuse
us so carelessly.
Do you know how much
it hurts us to
have our teacher distrust us
like that?
Please apologize.
Apologize!
I'm sorry.
If you understand,
then that's fine.
I'll tell you this, if you can't
show that you're innocent,
then I'll go to my parents.
Miyabi's mom is the president
of the PTA.
It can't be helped.
We can't have a pervert
homeroom teacher.
Shut up! What do you think
you're doing!
Stop it!
SORIMACHI TAKASHI
MATSUSHIMA NANAKO
KONDÔ YOSHIMASA
ENJÔJI AYA
KOBAYASHI MASAHIRO
IDA KUNIHIKO
KIRARI
IKEUCHI HIROYUKI
YAMAZAKI YÛTA
TOKUYAMA HIDENORI
KUBOZUKA YÔSUKE
NAKAMURA AIMI
KURODA MIKI
OGURI SHUN
FUJIKI NAOHITO
MABUCHI ERIKA
TATEISHI RYÔKO
ÔTSUKA YOSHIE
KIMURA TAE
YAMAZAKI MITSURU
NAKAO AKIRA
SHIRAKAWA YUMI
English Subtitles by
STUDIO NEW MEDIA
Subtitles Edited and Timed by
SCHWEFELHEXAFLUORID
D-ADDICTS
www.d-addicts.com
Directed by
AKABANE HIROSHI
A Production of
KANSAI TEREBI & AVEC
Goodbye! Don't wander around,
go straight home!
Okay!
Oh, Fuyutsuki-sensei.
Um, I...
Oh, I'm pooped today.
BEER
That hit the spot!
Fuyutsuki-sensei!
Oh, Miyuki!
Long time no see!
I think it's been since we
graduated from college!
- How've you been?
- I'm fine!
It looks like you're fully
a teacher already.
You think so?
You must be the favorite
with the students.
No, that's not true.
Oh, sorry I'm dressed
like this.
I just got back from Paris.
Oh, excuse me.
Hello?
Oh yes, thanks!
Oh, tomorrow?
That's fine.
I think I want to eat o-sushi.
Oh, thank you!
Then I'll be looking
forward to it!
I met him in the plane.
He's an actor.
He's been pestering me lately.
- Looks like you're busy.
- Yeah, well.
C'mon, let's go out
and eat somewhere next time!
Teachers have a lot of time
during summer vacation, right?
Well, yes.
Okay then, next time!
Give me a call,
Fuyutsuki-sensei.
- Thanks.
- See you!
Bye bye!
Why did she have to pass
the exam and I didn't?
"I met him in the plane.
He's an actor."
Gimme a break!
Couldn't be, right?
Hello, this is Fuyutsuki.
Azusa, it's Dad.
What happened?
Oh nothing. Are you going
to come home for summer?
Mom's worried about you.
I don't know yet, there's
still a lot of things.
Is there some problem
at school?
Oh no, it's nothing.
Well, this is from 30 years
of experience as a teacher.
As long as you face your
students sincerely, it'll work out.
Hang in there!
Mom and I, we're very happy
that you're
working hard at a Tokyo school.
I know that.
I'll phone again.
Bye!
RESIGNATION
Oh man! I didn't know you were
into this kind of stuff!
Next time you meet your mistress,
ask her out!
This ain't funny, dumb ass!
You say that, but I bet you've
got bruises all over your body.
Geeze, go home already!
You really drive me nuts,
hurry and get out of here!
Oh, I see.
Is that any way to talk to someone
who could help you solve
the riddle of this picture?
- W-W-W-Wait! Sit!
- Really?
I'm just in your way, aren't I?
Just tell me, 'kay?
Okay, here.
It's easy to do this with PC's now.
Take a good look at this,
the texture and color between
the face and body
doesn't match.
You're right.
It's really popular on the Internet.
They put idol's faces
on the bodies of magazine
and porno pictures.
There were rumors about that
with those nudes, remember?
But you know, it's because you
might be inclined to do this.
Kikuchi's the only one
who could do this.
He's always saying there's nothing
he can't do on a PC.
He's even doing stuff on
his PC during class.
We were classmates
in intermediate school,
so I know him pretty well.
Kikuchi was a snob
because of his high IQ
and would always make fools
of the teachers.
It has to be him.
He did all kinds of things
to make the last
homeroom teacher,
and the one before, quit.
What do you want?
Did you make these
fake pictures?
- C'mon, Kikuchi.
- That's right.
Why did you do this?
No reason really.
It was just a prank.
A prank?
I'm very sorry.
I apologized now.
What's up with your attitude?
Are you going to hit me?
Here, go ahead.
But I'll report it
to the teachers' board.
After that, please talk
to my lawyer.
In any case, I don't think you'll
be able to stay at this school.
Is that okay with you?
What a smart aleck.
Well talk about this later.
Everyone, take your seats!
So, where were we today?
Hey you, what are you doing?
I'm going home.
Didn't I just say, we're going
to proceed with the lesson?
There's no reason
to restrict me here.
What?
Rather than listen to your lecture,
it'd be better for me
to study at home.
You see, I don't consider
someone with
as low an IQ as you
as a teacher.
If you'll excuse me...
Did something happen?
It seems that Kikuchi from
2-4 is boycotting class.
What?
In my seven years as a teacher,
I've never seen something like this.
It was a mistake for someone like
Onizuka to be a teacher after all.
School isn't as easy now
as when he was around.
You need teachers with
more enthusiasm.
Like you?
Kotani-sensei, please!
Well, I think Kikuchi is up
to something.
He's the top suspect in the previous
class' 2-4 teacher bullying.
This was his doing too,
wasn't it?
What? Is that true?
If you're so concerned about it,
then you should take over.
That's right. You're always
saying he's the best,
he's got a 100% chance
of getting into Tôdai.
If he quits like this,
it'll reflect badly on this school.
Yes, that's certainly true.
Tashigara-sensei's got
a complex
because Kikuchi has
a higher IQ than him.
Well, I'm glad we don't have any
students like him in my class.
Right, Fuyutsuki-sensei?
Well, yes.
You must bring Kikuchi back
to school immediately!
Yoshito, I brought a snack.
So, why don't you eat
with us tomorrow?
Your father's home.
I'll pass.
It's not like we have anything
to talk about anyway.
Isn't it stuffy in here like this?
Excuse me, Mom,
but I can study by myself.
Do you best, okay?
I WAS REALLY SURPRISED WHEN YOU
SUDDENLY WENT HOME TODAY,
BUT THAT WAS YOUR PLAN,
WASN'T IT? MIYABI
OF COURSE, ACCORDING
TO MY CALCULATIONS,
ONIZUKA SHOULD BE OUT
OF HERE SOON.
- Yoshito, your teacher...
- Yo, Kikuchi!
Wow, this is a great room!
Woah! Is this all yours?
Did you finish all these?
You know this one, I can
never get my hands on it.
Can I try it out?
I see, trying to get friendly.
What a predictable pattern.
Trying that is useless.
Whatever you say won't convince
me to return to school.
And dragging me back
by force is useless.
- Do whatever you like.
- Huh?
If you don't want to go school,
then there's no need to come.
Then what did you come
here for?
It's that Uchiyamada.
He kept pestering me to come.
Alright then, I'll be going.
Sorry to bother you.
Oh, could you tell him
I was here.
Oh yeah, Kikuchi.
I almost forgot to ask you
something really important.
I want you to make me some
fake pictures with these.
- What?
- Got it?
This face... with this body.
No wait, maybe this one.
Ah, I'll leave the details to you.
Okay?
I'm not asking for free,
I'll give you 10,000 yen.
Not enough? I can't give
you any more,
I don't get much of a salary,
you know!
Okay, I'll be looking
forward to it.
S-So you left right after that?
Well of course. He didn't
want to come back,
so there wasn't anything
I could do.
Did you really try
to convince him?
Yes.
Of course!
I was at it for hours!
But that cold hearted guy didn't
listen to me at all...
Never mind already!
It's too much for you.
Nakamaru-sensei,
you go instead.
Um, I'm not good at dealing
with those types...
What are you saying?
You're the school supervisor,
aren't you?
Oh! How about
Fuyutsuki-sensei?
Hold on! Why me?
Weren't you his advisor?
Besides, for problems like this,
I think the softer approach
of a woman might be better.
I see.
Alright then.
Fuyutsuki-sensei,
we're counting on you.
Thank you,
Can I help you?
Kikuchi-kun,
would you please come
to school?
- Why should I?
- Well, you see...
There's a lot that's enjoyable.
You can make lots
of great memories.
You're just saying that.
The head teacher made
you come anyway.
- That's not true!
- It must be terrible.
Unless you convince me,
it'll be bad for the teachers.
That's not it!
I'm thinking about you.
Then do you think school
really is enjoyable?
I do.
So you intend to remain
a teacher?
- Yes, well.
- How about marriage?
Is there someone you're
seeing now?
Not right now...
Anyway, that's not what
I came to talk about!
Then it'll be a workplace
marriage.
What?
Haven't you heard? 85%
of teachers now
get married within
the workplace.
Because teachers don't have much
opportunity to meet others.
Well, yes...
So who are the bachelors
at our school?
Hakamada from
physical education.
Man, but he's one sweaty guy...
There's Teshigawara from
mathematics.
I dunno, he looks like he might
have a Oedipus complex...
Then there's...
I guess that leaves Onizuka.
Don't be ridiculous!
If I were to marry someone like that,
I'd rather remain single!
Is that how you really feel?
By the time you get old, you
won't have much of a pension.
I suppose so.
What would you do about
a place?
If you're going to buy a condo,
you better think about it soon.
What about savings? You have
to be careful where to put it now -
banks are closing all the time
nowadays.
Yes, I guess so.
Teacher, you're 25 already,
right?
You better start taking
things seriously!
Thirty will roll around before
you know it!
I suppose so.
I've got cram school,
if you'll excuse me.
Do your best!
Just what am I doing?
Thank you for waiting.
But this is really unexpected,
that you would call me out.
Is this a welcome party for me?
Of course not!
What are you so angry about?
The incident with that fake
picture is cleared up.
There's a more important
problem!
- What's that?
- It's about Kikuchi-kun.
Oh, so it was no good?
Well, he's so cocky,
isn't he.
How can you be so nonchalant
about this?
It's because of you that
the head teacher...
Fuyutsuki-sensei.
What are you doing?
Well, I thought your face is
wonderful even when angry.
Please stop it!
Gotcha.
Fuyutsuki-sensei,
where are you going?
Will you please cut that out!
What's up?
Please convince Kikuchi.
If you don't clear this up,
I'll end up having to take
responsibility for this.
Don't worry! Just leave him
alone and he'll come back.
I can't believe that.
It's because of the teachers'
posturing that kids take advantage.
I should know because
I was one of those kids.
Hey, never mind that,
let's go get something to eat!
My students did
a lot of research,
on where the good Italian
places are.
How about here?
Excuse me,
but I've wanted to know this,
why did a person like you ever
want to become a teacher?
- It's the same as you.
- Like me?
There's nothing else I want to be.
That's how you feel, right?
There seems to be
a misunderstanding,
so I'll tell you right now,
there's other things I'd rather
be doing.
What would that be?
Why should I tell you?
C'mon tell me,
you brought it up.
Anyway, I didn't want
to become a teacher.
When I was looking for work,
I was made to apply for teaching
and I was accepted,
so I didn't have a choice.
Didn't have a choice?
- So what?
- That stinks!
Why does someone like me who
wants to become a teacher have
to suffer while someone like you
can become one so easily?
You know, just because
you couldn't study
and make it, don't cry to me!
You probably cheated on
your graduation exam!
You know, away from the office
you aren't so nice.
My calling you a Madonna
of a teacher was wrong.
Well, you wouldn't understand
how I feel!
Every day I come home
from school suffering!
If you hate school so much,
then you should quit!
If you do that, then maybe one
other person like me
will be able to become
a teacher.
Okay, alright! I'll quit!
And why do I have to sit next
to you every day anyway!
Yeah right. You don't even have
your resignation written.
- I do!
- Show me!
I do, see!
What are you doing?
That's strange...
Go on, persuade him.
Kikuchi-kun,
this is something else!
Yes. It's a class on Probability
and it's pretty hard,
but it's much more fulfilling
than sitting
in some worthless lecture
in school.
But you know, there's a lot
of good things in school.
Like what, for example?
Well...
You see, I wasn't suppose
to be at that school anyway.
What do you mean?
I got sick in intermediate school
during the placement exams.
Otherwise there would have
been no way
I would have ended up there.
If I look at it over my whole life,
it'll just be a little mistake.
It'll be fine if I get into Tôdai.
So high school is just
a rehearsal to me.
I'm going just
because I have no choice.
Because you have no choice...
That's right.
You shouldn't take it too lightly,
Kikuchi.
There's a lot of things
you can't do, I'll show you.
What are you talking about?
I'm talking about social skills.
Sorry, but I've never lost at this.
Hold on, I wasn't ready.
Dammit, I can't loose.
How uncool.
Excuse me.
What is that you want me
to learn from you?
If you'll pardon me.
- Hold it there, bro!
- What do you want?
Don't play innocent when
you bumped into someone.
- Ow, ow, ow!
- Hey, are you okay?
What are you going to do
about this, he's in pain!
How can he be after just that.
Hey, are you calling me a liar?
Okay, I get it.
You're just after money anyway.
How much, 20,000, 30,000?
What a cocky jerk!
He's making fools of us.
Let's teach him a lesson.
You're from Fuda University,
right?
Won't you get expelled for this?
Besides, my father knows
people in the police.
So what of it!
Yeah, so what of it!
Who do you think you are?
Kikuchi-kun, what's going on?
He's my teacher,
he's a karate expert.
You better go before
you get hurt.
Hmm?
Who's your teacher?
What do you mean?
But you don't think of me as
a teacher, right?
Stop joking!
Kikuchi's smart, so he should be
able to figure out what to do.
Right?
Do you know what will happen if
the school finds out about this?
That's right, Onizuka-sensei!
Stop joking!
What kind of teacher ignores
his student!
That's right, please come back!
Please help me!
Teacher...
Shut up!
Don't call me "teacher" only
when it's convenient.
Always be gracious?
And you're the one who
belittles teachers.
Just because you're a minor
and you get into trouble
you expect me to protect you?
Isn't that expecting too much?
If you're a man, then take
your lumps like a man!
Onizuka-sensei!
Where in the world is there
a teacher that would ignore
his student when he's being
attacked by punks?
My son is saying he doesn't want
to go to school anymore!
What is this school going
to do about this?
If he was at the scene, then why
did he leave it to the police?
I'm very sorry.
You can't play dumb, Director.
I know you're there.
This time, I'll have Onizuka
take responsibility!
Do you understand?
Isn't there something else
we can do?
If we don't have Onizuka
quit by tomorrow,
Kikuchi said he'll withdraw
from school!
The most important thing
for the student
is to attend school every day.
I don't know what would
happen to Kikuchi-kun.
I understand what you're
saying, but...
Director!
I understand.
What are you going to do,
Onitchi?
At this rate, you really
will have to quit.
That Kikuchi's serious.
Serves you right, Onizuka.
Just a few more hours.
I'm home!
What's wrong?
Will you have a word with her!
This girl does nothing
but date guys!
She hasn't gone to her
college classes!
It doesn't matter,
I'm getting good scores!
That's not the point!
You have to start thinking
about your future!
Well I won't be a bother to you,
so please don't worry.
I'm concerned about you,
how dare you talk
like that to me!
Oh geeze!
Do you think you grew up
by yourself?
Who do you think raised you?
- I never asked you to.
- Quiet!
- Shape up!
- Papa!
Dear!
What are you grinning for?
Be firm with her for once!
- Be firm?
- Yes, firm.
Yoshiko.
Yoshiko!
What do you want?
Dad'll be disappointed...
Are you okay?
- Looks sore.
- It's nothing.
But it worked out perfect!
I didn't think it'd work this fast.
So Onizuka's out tomorrow.
Guess we overestimated him.
What's up?
But you know, that Fuyutsuki's
not much better.
I thought she was a better
teacher,
but I'll have to change how
I look at her.
She's on the same level
as Onizuka.
She's just pretty.
She's got nothing in her.
Nothing.
Like she's riding
a wood horse.
Please wait!
It's only for a minute,
so please!
- What are you doing?
- I have to talk to him.
I'm sorry Yoshito,
she forced her way in.
I'll have her leave.
It's okay.
So what did you want to talk about?
You are mistaken.
You should stop taking
adults so lightly.
People like you always end up
regretting it in the future.
You see, that's because...
because people...
people can't live by themselves.
Excuse me, could you please
be clear about
what you want to say?
It's that kind of condescending
attitude toward others...
Kikuchi! You there?
- What are you doing?
- Kikuchi, you're mistaken.
I was just told that.
You said that high school was
just a rehearsal
before you get into Tôdai,
right?
Rather than getting into a good
university or finding a good job,
I feel that finding good friends
is more important.
Are you trying to appeal
to my emotions? How pathetic.
If you look at everything like that,
you'll never make friends.
Friends that don't study,
I don't need that.
Listen you.
I don't have anything to learn
from you.
What's that?
Because everything you say
is written in a textbook.
Is it so much fun
stuffing your brain
with that stuff day after day?
Do you enjoy thinking about
scores every day?
Humans, they should cherish
life more, don't you think?
They should cherish the present.
Life is a collection of that.
So life isn't a rehearsal for that.
Every day is the real thing.
You should live today
to the fullest.
If you don't, won't you
feel sorry for yourself?
What are you people doing?
Please wait just a little more,
this is an important moment.
What are your doing
to my son!
Just a little more.
Yoshito, are you alright?
You know...
When I was in high school
I was a troublemaker.
I hardly went to school.
Before I knew it, I was expelled.
When I couldn't go was
when I first realized,
that school was a great thing.
There's a lot of friends
and lots of fun things.
When I got this old, I wanted
even more to go to school.
That's why I became a teacher.
Because, if I became
a teacher,
I could be in school
until I die, right?
That's why I'm really happy now.
I want you to be like that too.
I want you to like school.
I want to you like it now.
If you realize it later like me,
it's too late, Kikuchi!
Ah, stop it!
'Nuff rain already, let's quit.
Why, Onitchi?
We almost had him.
Yeah, it was making a real
impression on Kikuchi!
Yeah, and we're going
to win the bet, you know.
I don't care.
Sorry 'bout that, Kikuchi.
You see we had a bet going.
Whether I could convince
you or not.
Nanako suggested it
and it sounded like fun.
But if you came
to school because of this,
it'd go against my policy.
What are you saying Onitchi?
At this rate you're going
to be fired!
And besides... what you
were saying became real.
Those weren't rehearsed lines.
That was your true feelings,
right?
I don't really get it.
But you know,
it felt like what I was saying was
not for Kikuchi, but for myself.
Because if he doesn't come
to school, then I'd be in a bind.
But you know, doing this
kind of stuff, I don't like it.
Later, Kikuchi.
What about us?
If you're fired, then we
won't be able to see you!
Listen...
Even if I quit school,
I'll still be with you.
It looks like the rain has lifted,
hasn't it?
Today, I have an unfortunate
disappointing announcement.
Today, Onizuka-sensei will
be leaving us.
Just when he was getting
along with you all.
I'm sure Onizuka-sensei is
very disappointed too,
but he has personal affairs
that he must deal with.
You, why?
If I'm the reason for his
personal affairs,
then I don't think you have
to quit, Onizuka-sensei.
Sir, will there be anything else?
Okay, let's make today
a great school day!
He did it!
Kikuchi, what's
the meaning of this?
I know,
you've got something even more
interesting up your sleeve.
Sorry, but I'm out of this.
You see...
He's not a teacher.
What the hell are you
talking about?
Besides, hanging out with you
guys is no fun.
Hey Kikuchi!
Hey, you got those pictures?
Woah! These are great!
You really are a genius!
So, could you do one more?
Whatcha laughing about?
'Kay, got it?
What happened,
Fuyutsuki-sensei?
You look so happy.
- What? Really?
- Did something good happen?
Yes, well.
Onizuka-sensei...
Yes?
I...
This is the first time since
I became a teacher...
That I've been so inspired.
Oh, really?
Hey!
What is this?
Um, well, um, it's...
Is that why you were taking
all those pictures of me?
I take back everything
about being inspired!
You better owe up to this,
you better!
Kikuchi!
- Hey, join us!
- Yeah!
Sorry, gotta pass,
I've got cram school.
Hey, but this is on your way.
Well, going this way is faster.
Good luck, Kikuchi!
Hey, isn't that Noboru?
- Where?
- Over there.
What's that idiot doing?
2016-04